Finding Aid for Satakunta Region immigrant letters, 1880-1964
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Karvia, letters to
  - Hilja Mahlamäki
    - from: Hilda Kauppila., undated; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Fanny Korpela. Ore., 1951; 2 items (Reel 9)
    - from:Hellevi Kauppila., undated; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Kyllikki Kokko. Ont., 1964; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Helmi Komulainen. Wash., 1963; 3 items (Reel 9)
  - Lahja Perälä
    - from: Esther Salo. Minn., 1956; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Joel Kannisto
    - from: Hilma Halme. Ont., 1955; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Juho Mäenpää
    - from: Jaakko Maenpaa., undated; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Lempi Aarnituli
    - from: Hilma Neva. Minn. (l item), 1963 (Reel 9)
  - Anselm Ala-Korte
    - from: Aliina Ollila. Watton, Mich., Negaunee, Mich., 1930-1946; 19 items (Reel 9)
  - Juulia Hauskamaa
    - from: Linnea Laine., 1960-1963; 3 items (Reel 9)
  - Johannes Hälli
    - from: Ludvik Halli. Ont., Ill., 1910-1931; 3 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Siimoni Halli. Ill., 1939-1947; 3 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Eero Halli. Ont., 1933-1962; 11 items (Reel 9)
  - Erhard Puisto
    - from: Hulda Mattsson. Eben, Mich., 1953; 5 items (Reel 9)
  - Lilja Rahkamaa
    - from: Sigrid Kuusela. Ont., 1955; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Emilia Valli. Minn., 1956; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Hilda Hill. Minn., 1961; 1 items (Reel 9)
  - Ilona Rahvola
    - from: Hilja Nordlund. Ont., 1949-1952; 2 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Martti Nordlund. Ont., 1946-1950; 3 items (Reel 9)
  - Hilja Ruoho
    - from: Sigrid Kuusela. Ont., 1962; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Liina Kauppi. Allen Park, Mich., undated; 1 items (Reel 9)
    - from: Sylvi Lustila. Ont., 1962-1964; 3 items (Reel 9)
  - Lea Hakola
    - from: Paul Hall. Ont., 1917-1946; 12 items (Reel 9)
  - Aale Harju
    - from: Juho Huhtamäki. Minn., 1947-1962; 6 items (Reel 10)
  - Lyydi Kivelä
    - from:Hilda Kauppila. Minn., 1958-1962; 2 items (Reel 10)
  - Juho Leivo
    - from: Vante Lammi. Minn., 1911-1912; 2 items (Reel 10)
  - Yrjö Mäki-Koivisto
    - from: Juha Huhtamaki. Minn., 1952-1969; 3 items (Reel 10)
  - Kauko Närvä
    - from: Ville Sarkkila. Minn., 1946; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Miina Ylikorte
    - from: Selma Sehmirt. Ill., 1959-1962; 2 items (Reel 10)
  - Hilma Erkkilä
    - from: Lempi Kulmala. Ohio, 1955-1963; 7 items (Reel 10)
  - Eino Kivistö
    - from: Emmi Seppanen. Ont., 1964; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Siiri Peijanniemi
    - from: Ida Frantila. N.Y., 1911; 5 items (Reel 10)
    - from: Ida Peijanniemi. N.J., N.Y., 1912; 23 items (Reel 10)
  - Anto Puisto
    - from: M. Mattsson
      - Ewen, Mich., 1945-1946; 10 items (Reel 10)
      - Wis., 1947; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Frans Hautaluoma
    - from: Aarne Autio. Mont., 1960 (Reel 10)
  - Vihtori Soini
    - from: Alma Heino. Minn., Fla., 1954-1964; 3 items (Reel 10)
  - Vihtori Nikola
    - from: R. Ullas. Ont., 1950; 2 items (Reel 10)
  - Hilda Marttila
    - from: Sanna Koski. Ont., 1954-1963; 2 items (Reel 10)
  - Varma Mäntyjoki
    - from: Ida Hirvela. Fla., N.H., 1963; 6 items (Reel 10)
  - Martta Ala-Hakkola
    - from: Sylvia Lustila. Ont., 1935-1947; 9 items (Reel 10)
  - Emili Alkkiomäki
    - from: Mandi Fors. Md., 1953-1957; 3 items (Reel 10)
  - Lempi Harju
    - from: E. Niemi. Ont., 1959; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Lyydia Isomäki
    - from: Lea Valli.
      - Minn., Ont., Ill., Alta., 1922-1958; 34 items (Reel 10)
  - Yrjö Itäluoma
    - from: Hilma Niemela. Mass., Fla. (3 items, 1956 (Reel 10)
  - Anni Järvenpää
    - from: Mary Jarvenpaa. Mass., Ont., 1947-1952; 5 items (Reel 10)
  - Jaakko Kannisto
    - from: Svante Ylinen. Mont., 1919; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Olavi Kiviniemi
    - from: Hulda Otava. Minn., 1939-1945; 2 items (Reel 10)
  - Jooseppi Kiviniemi
    - from: John Otava. Minn., 1917-1969; 5 items (Reel 10)
  - Olavi Kiviniemi
    - from: Leo Otava. Minn., 1917-1941; 2 items (Reel 10)
  - Jooseppi Kiviniemi
    - from: Amalia Ruha. Minn., 1938-1961; 5 items (Reel 10)
  - Olavi Kiviniemi
    - from: Yoivo Niskala. Minn., 1946; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Rauni Luodetlahti
    - from: Hilda Lahde. Ont., 1954-1969; 5 items (Reel 10)
  - Kaisa Lähdenniemi
    - from: Svante Marjasuo. Negaunee, Mich., 1945; 11 items (Reel 10)
  - Katri Lähdenniemi
    - from: Emil Ruoko. Ill., 1945; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Lempi Matalamäki
    - from: H. Wuori, I. Pitanta. Ont., Cal., 1951-1953; 3 items (Reel 10)
  - Vilho Matalamäki
    - from: various. Mass., Sweden, Ont., Minn., Cal., 1912-1959; 51 items (Reel 10)
  - Hilkka Niemenmaa
    - from: Nestor Maki. Minn., 1903-1916; 2 items (Reel 10)
  - Jenny Pentinmäki
    - from: Esther Salo. Calif., Minn., 1946-1953; 12 items (Reel 10)
  - Ville Pentinmäki
    - from: Esther Salo. Minu., 1940-1958; 4 items (Reel 10)
  - Impi Puisto
    - from: Hilda Kauppila. Minn., 1952; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Aili Rantaviita
    - from: Emil Koskinen. Covington, Mich., 1962-1963; 3 items (Reel 10)
  - Helvi Riihiluomanperä
    - from: Alfred Haapanen. Houghton, Mich., 1959-1961; 3 items (Reel 10)
  - Ilmari Vaho
    - from: Mary Kallio. Conn., Ont., 1945-1948; 5 items (Reel 10)
    - from: Osi Niemi.
      - Detroit, Mich., 1922; 1 items (Reel 10)
      - Ont., 1946; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Martta Viertola
    - from: J. Rostedt. R.I., 1953-1962; 5 items (Reel 10)
  - Suorna Ylitalo
    - from: Emilia Valli. Minn., 1950; 10 items (Reel 10)
  - Unknown Recipient
    - from: Miina Maki. Minn., 1904; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Samuel Ylinen
    - from: W. Ylinen. Minn., 1920; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Heimo Kivistö
    - from: Vaino Kivisto. Mt., 1948; 1 items (Reel 10)
    - from: Emmi Seppanen. Ont., 1952; 1 items (Reel 10)
    - from: Ate Kivisto. Ont., 1952; 1 items (Reel 10)
    - fromea Manner. Ont., 1953; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Emma Lustila
    - from: Eemil Maki., 1959; 1 items (Reel 10)
    - from: Sylvi Lustila. Ont., 1963; 3 items (Reel 10)
  - Maria Niskala
    - from: Sigrid Kuusela. Ont., 1960-1961; 5 items (Reel 10)
  - Urpo Rahkomaa
    - from: Arvo Pajunen. Ont., 1959; 1 items (Reel 10)
  - Tuomas Ojanperä
    - from: Esteri Niemi. England, Ont., undated; 2 items (Reel 10)
  - Bertta Koskimäki
    - from: Sylvi Lustila. Ont., 1959-1964; 28 items (Reel 10)
    - from: A. Niemi. Ont., 1959-1964; 73 items (Reel 10)
    - from: A. Niemi. Ont., 1960; 5 items (Reel 11)
  - Toini Mantila
    - from: Nikolai Jarvenpaa. Ont., 1925; 2 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Sylvia Hakkila. Ont., 1925; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Martta Mäki-Niskala
    - from: Arvo, Hietaniemi. Quebec, 1955-1963; 3 items (Reel 11)
  - Rauha Malmila
    - from: Sandra Mannila. Ont., 1959; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Eino Oikonen
    - from: Arvi Oikonen. Ont., 1945-1962; 17 items (Reel 11)
  - Alma Sievi-Korte
    - from: Arvi Oikonen. Ont., 1947-1948; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Hilda Penttilg
    - from: Lilja Rantala. Ont., 1937; 8 items (Reel 11)
  - Vilho Mastomäki
    - from: Martta Maki. Ont., 1939; 1 items (Reel 11)
  - Lempi Koivisto
    - from: Elma Kallio. Ont., 1964; 3 items (Reel 11)
  - Hilda Hietanen
    - from: Raimo Neuvonen. Australia, 1961; 1 items (Reel 11)
  - Eedla Lehtimäki
    - from: Lea Lehtimaki. Que., 1963; 1 items (Reel 11)
  - Arvo Ala-Korte
    - from: Paul Ollila. Negaunee, Mich., 1946; 1 items (Reel 11)
  - Hilkka Rantala
    - from: Fanny Nurkkala. Watton, Mich., 1963; 1 items (Reel 11)
- Kihniö, letters to
  - Tyyne Taupila
    - from: Julius Kolehmainen. Hancock, Mich., 1957; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Kalevi Yli-Välitalo
    - from: Iisak Jokinen. Minn., 1959; 1 items (Reel 11)
  - Signe Leppänen
    - from: Jussi Ruoho. Minn., undated; 1 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Joseph Ruoho. Minn., 1933; 2 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Laura Ruoho. Minn., 1925-1928; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Vihtori Taupila
    - from: John Rintala. Mass., 1963; 1 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Arvo Rintala. Mass., 1964; 1 items (Reel 11)
  - Mariana Puska
    - from: Selma Maki. Ont., Mass., Minn., 1959-1961; 4 items (Reel 11)
  - Juho Peuramäki
    - from: Vilhelm Peuramäki. Ont., 1961; 1 items (Reel 11)
  - Hilda Riihimaa
    - from: S. Ojala. Ont., Minn., 1946-1957; 5 items (Reel 11)
  - Elmi Mäkelä
    - from: Valter Lehto. Mass., 1962; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Werner Kiviniemi
    - from: Kilja Justi, Gust Nikula. Minn., Fla., 1960-1964; 25 items (Reel 11)
- Kiikka, letters to
  - Veikko Anttila
    - from: Marin Anttila. Minn., 1960-1964; 4 items (Reel 11)
- Kiikoinen, letters to
  - Elma Antila
    - from: Martin Anttila. Minn., 1948-1963; 9 items (Reel 11)
  - Toivo Jaakola
    - from: Tilda Lahti. Minn., 1957-1959; 2 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Kalle Jaakola. Minn., 1923; 2 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Tyyne Lahti. Minn., 1920-1964; 4 items (Reel 11)
  - Eila Myllymaa
    - from: Evert Myllymaa. Minn., Ore., 1948-1950; 3 items (Reel 11)
  - Johan Lahtinen
    - from: unnamed. Ont., 1908-1956; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Frans Valtanen
    - from: Oskari Valtanen. Munising, Mich., Ironwood, Mich., 1912-1962; 11 items (Reel 11)
- Kiukainen, letters to
  - Emil Lindroos
    - from: August Valila. Minn., 1950-1961; 10 items (Reel 11)
    - from:Martti Salo. Minn., 1957; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Sylvi Haavisto, Eine Manner, Eevi Vataja
    - from: Frans Mannisto, Mary Heikkinen, Olga Oksa. photo, 1 items (Reel 11)
  - Frans Kaitale
    - from: Mikko Muntter. photos, 3 items (Reel 11)
  - Helmi Salomaa
    - from: Elli Tuomi. Verm., Conn., Mass., 1939-1941; 7 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Eine Pohjola. N.Y., 1947; 2 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Reino Pohjola. N.Y., 1945-1969; 5 items (Reel 11)
  - Aina Ylijoki
    - from: Frans Ylijoki. Mass., 1962-1963; 4 items (Reel 11)
  - Helmi Kylämarttila
    - from: Frans Pakola. Minn., 1947; 3 items (Reel 11)
  - Helga Laiho
    - from: Vaino Aarnio. Mass., 1961-1964; 3 items (Reel 11)
  - Manda Lindell, Eine Manner, Manne Martinsuo
    - from: Selma Lepisto, Antti Lepisto, Signe Lepisto, Laura Nordman. Calif., 1963-1964; 6 items (Reel 11)
  - Manne Martinsuo
    - from: Helmi Surmont. Cal., 1963; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Helmi Mattila
    - from: Fanny Salonen. Mass., 1962-1964; 3 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Elli Routhier. Ont., 1953-1963; 4 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Aino Kubata. Ont., 1960; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Elma Outola
    - from: Fanny Salonen. Wis., Mass., 1963-1964; 5 items (Reel 11)
  - Pauli Latoja
    - from: Vaino Helkio, Helmi Helmi Gronroos. photo (l items) (Reel 11)
  - Eevi Nurmi
    - from: Vaino Makikallio. photo, 1 items (Reel 11)
  - Eevi Laine
    - from: Uahja Tanner. photo, 1 items (Reel 11)
  - Altti Tarkki
    - from: Neemi Niskala. Ohio, 1964; 2 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Abel Stark. Ohio, 1962; 3 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Leah Sjoblom. Ohio, 1963; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Eeva Bergroos, Toini Pere, Väinö Pere, Toini Mäntylä
    - from: Bert Salomaa, Onni Herrala, Saima Troitte, Elli. Routhier. Ont., 1962-1963; 3 items (Reel 11)
  - Jenny Jokela
    - from: Veikko Jokela. Mass. (.2 items), 1963 (Reel 11)
- Kokemäki, letters to
  - Frans Aakula
    - from: Niilo Valtonen. Brazil, 1962; 1 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Frans Vehko. Minn., 1960-1961; 4 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Frans Suominen. Minn., 1930-1961; 2 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Kustaa Aakula. Minn., 1909-1962; 12 items (Reel 11)
  - Emma Ikala
    - from: Kaisa Falt. N.J., 1929-1964; 37 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Elizabeth Blomquist. N.Y., 1938-1963; 7 items (Reel 11)
  - Väinö Aakula
    - from: Frank Vehka. Minn., 1960-1961; 7 items (Reel 11)
  - Yrjö Iso-Ikala
    - from: Jalmari Ikala
      - Ironwood, Mich., 1905-1906; 2 items (Reel 11)
      - Eng, 1940; 1 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Evert Ikala. Minn., 1914-1917; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Manta Salminen
    - from: Ella Mankinen. Maine, 1945-1954; 21 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Alma Lehto. Ont., 1946-1947; 3 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Elsa Vataja. Maine, Ont., 1951-1963; 7 items (Reel 11)
  - Ellen Oittinen
    - from: Johannes Jansson. Australia, 1960; 3 items (Reel 11)
  - Yrjö Virtanen
    - from: Emma Tamminen. Mass., 1955; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Helvi Mela
    - from: Juhani Valtanen. Ohio, 1955-1963; 6 items (Reel 11)
  - Sylvi Iivonen
    - from: Hilda Lindell, Hilma Ilola. photos, 4 items (Reel 11)
  - Alma Virtanen
    - from: Hilja Metsisto. Mass., 1960; 2 items (Reel 11)
  - Elli Vainio
    - from: Eemeli Vainio. Wash., Ont., 1919-1932; 6 items (Reel 11)
- Kullaa, letters to
  - Maija Kylä-Paavola
    - from: Ivar Leikas. Minn., 1914-1922; 8 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Mary Niemi. N.J., 1914; 3 items (Reel 11)
    - from: Mary Niemi. N.J., Pa., Fla., 1914-1951; 28 items (Reel 12)
    - from: Ida Hill. Wash., 1948-1956; 15 items (Reel 12)
    - from: Wihtori Salminen. Que., 1931; 2 items (Reel 12)
  - Vihtori Kaunisto
    - from: Frans Dahl. N.Y. (.1 items), 1921 (Reel 12)
  - Aino Niemi
    - from: Tilda Johnson. Minn., 1949; 2 items (Reel 12)
  - Tekla Railo
    - from: Hilma West. Minn., 1952-1958; 5 items (Reel 12)
  - Juho Railo
    - from: Juho Railo, photos, passport, 4 items (Reel 12)
    - from: Fiina Lammi. Sweden, Ont., 1954-1963; 9 items (Reel 12)
  - Annikki Seppälä
    - from: Olga Lumme
      - Wash., Ill., N.Y., N.J., Ohio, Mass., Wis.,. Fla., 1909-1934; 83 items (Reel 12)
      - Detroit, Mich., 1910-1928; 12 items (Reel 12)
  - Aino Salonen
    - from: Ida Salonen. Minn., 1940-1947; 7 items (Reel 12)
  - Veikko Kiilo
    - from: Ida Mannisto. Minn., 1924-1936; 4 items (Reel 12)
  - Yrjö Lehtikangas
    - from: Vaino Kangas, Elli Eblom. Wis., 1963-1964; 10 items (Reel 12)
  - Aina Salo
    - from: Vaino Sills. N.Y., 1921-1963; 52 items (Reel 12)
  - Urpo Myllymäki
    - from: Juho Lindgren. Fla., 1963; 1 items (Reel 12)
  - Fenny Botsman
    - from: Liisi Vuori. Minn., 1963; 1 items (Reel 12)
  - Sanna Kaunisto
    - from: Toivo Niemi. Ont., 1926; 8 items (Reel 12)
  - Erkki Souko
    - from: Helmi Lahtinen. Ont., 1963; 2 items (Reel 12)
  - Martta Taimi
    - from: Elizabeth Kalliomaki. Mass., Fla., 1953-1961; 6 items (Reel 12)
  - Aarne Kallio
    - from: Sylvia Eehlhoff. Ishpeming, Mich., 1962; 1 items (Reel 12)
- Kyöliö, letters to
  - Anna Valli
    - from: Johannes Valli. Wash., 1960-1963; 3 items (Reel 12)
  - Esko Härkälä
    - from: Evert Makila. Chassell, Mich., 1941-1956; 13 items (Reel 12)
  - Emil Selin
    - from: Ilmari Selin. Minn., 1953-1962; 6 items (Reel 12)
  - Fanny Martti
    - from: Aina Malmi. Ore., 1958; 1 items (Reel 12)
    - from: Vihtori Makela. Minn., 1957; 1 items (Reel 12)
  - K. Mäki
    - from: various. Finland, N.Y., 1911; 4 items (Reel 12)
  - Esko Uusimaa
    - from: Fanny Anttonen. Mass., 1947-1948; 3 items (Reel 12)
  - Aino Salo
    - from: Anni Salo. Minn., 1957-1964; 10 items (Reel 12)
- Läppi Tl, letters to
  - Erland Heinilä
    - from: Viktor Nummela. Minn., Wash., 1901-1912; 27 items (Reel 12)
    - from: Vilho Heinila. Ont., 1924-1926; 6 items (Reel 12)
  - Aino Maijala
    - from: Victor Waurio. Ironwood, Mich., 1944-1969; 4 items (Reel 12)
  - Ellen Lehtola
    - from: Emanuel Maki. Maine, 1959-1969; 3 items (Reel 12)
  - Helvi Leino
    - from: Isak Jalonen. Ironwood, Mich., 1948; 1 items (Reel 12)
  - Lahja Kallio
    - from: Lizzie Hartman. Mass., 1906-1961; 59 items (Reel 12)
    - from: Victor Lahti. Mass., 1912-1953; 22 items (Reel 12)
    - from: Victor Lahti. Mass., 1959-1963; 9 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Aino Kanerva. Minn. Cal., 1921; 4 items (Reel 13)
  - Aili Seikkula
    - from: Ida Niemi. Wis., 1938; 1 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Violet Hovi. Minn., 1947; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Aino Seikkula
    - from: Vendla Salonen, Wictor Roos.
      - N.Y., N.J., Minn., Wis., 1905-1962; 13 items (Reel 13)
      - Bessemer, Mich., 1906-1907; 2 items (Reel 13)
      - Mass., Conn., Minn., Wis., Sask., 1909; 26 items (Reel 13)
  - Helvi Leino
    - from: Vihtor Elonen. Wis., 1945; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Aune Narvila
    - from: Sanna Nurmi. Wash., 1948; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Anni Anttila
    - from: Tekla Virta. Mass., 1956-1958; 5 items (Reel 13)
  - Anna Söderman
    - from: Laura Nordman. Calif., 1964; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Hilja Salminen
    - from: Hjalmar Lehtinen. N.H., 1961-1963; 4 items (Reel 13)
  - Aira Lehtonen
    - from: Viktor Lehtimaki. Ohio, 1927-1938; 4 items (Reel 13)
  - Nestor Nurmi
    - from: Edla Koski. N.Y., 1951-1952; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Tuula Lamminen
    - from: Ida Wiitanen. Mass., 1961; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Elli Salonen
    - from: various.
      - Ironwood, Mich., 1929; 1 items (Reel 13)
      - Wis., undated; 4 items (Reel 13)
      - Ironwood, Mich., 1962; 8 items (Reel 13)
      - Wis., 1963-1964; 7 items (Reel 13)
  - Frans Valtonen
    - from: T. Linjanen. Minn., Cal., 1946-1964; 20 items (Reel 13)
  - Aune Narvila
    - from: Ellen Nurmi. Wyo., 1929; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Kerttu Hunsala
    - from: Taimi Aaltonen. N.Y., 1964; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Raili Saherma
    - from: Helmi Surmont. Cal. (1 item, 1963 (Reel 13)
  - Lempi Kallio
    - from: Vilma Fredrickson. Mass., 1946; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Aino Laukola
    - from: Elli Lehtonen. Ont., 1960-1962; 5 items (Reel 13)
  - Väinö Uusitalo
    - from: Aarne Vainio. Minn., Ill., 1946-1957; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Maissi Perkiö
    - from: Eino Lehto. Minn., 1949; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Helmi Kyllänpää
    - from: Jaakko Linden. Mass., 1934; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Eine Leino
    - from: W. Pietila. Calif., 1963; 5 items (Reel 13)
- Lavia, letters to
  - Frans Laine
    - from: Emil Laine. Minn., 1930-1937; 2 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Toivo Koskinen., 1909; 1 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Urho Koskinen. Pa., 1911; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Roosa Aro
    - from: Salomon Telin. Ill., Wis., Ia., 1954-1964; 27 items (Reel 13)
  - Jussi Hakala
    - from: Kalle Hakala. South Range, Mich., 1950-1963; 3 items (Reel 13)
  - E. R. Wirtanen
    - from: Malakias Wirtanen. Minn., 1925; 1 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Martti Wirtanen. Minn., 1933-1949; 6 items (Reel 13)
  - Kustaa Maja
    - from: Walfred Rantanen. Minn., 1948; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Katri Kaapeli
    - from: Milja Haapala. Ohio, 1962; 1 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Helmi Matson. N.J., 1963-1964; 5 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Matilda Walton. Wis., 1963; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Matilda Lahdensuu
    - from: Lempi Maki. Minn. (l item), undated (Reel 13)
  - Hilja Laurila
    - from: Hilja Waara. Calif., 1948-1957; 3 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Selma Rantala. Ohio, undated; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Ellen Heinola
    - from: Emil Ranta. Chassell, Mich., 1924-1963; 9 items (Reel 13)
  - Into Viljanen
    - from: Lempi Pesio. S.D., 1945-1948; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Martti Nieminen
    - from: Pentti Saarinen. Ont., 1956-1962; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Lasse Lepistö
    - from: Lauri Lepisto. Ont., 1963; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Erkki Koivisto
    - from: Roy Helander. Mass., 1958; 1 items (Reel 13)
- Loimaa, letters to
  - Annikki Vihava
    - from: Robert Heikkila. Ont., 1903-1918; 2 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Sulho Kannisto. N.Y., N.J., 1924-1930; 14 items (Reel 13)
  - Nikolai Ylismäki
    - from: Anna Broberg. Mass., 1950-1962; 13 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Aino Halme. Massa, 1945-1961; 8 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Miina Ylismaki
      - Trout Creek, Mich., 1908; 1 items (Reel 13)
      - Colto:, Mass., 1909-1954; 4 items (Reel 13)
  - Antti Laakso
    - from: Antti Tanttu. Minn., 1956; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Hanna Lehtisaari
    - from: Kaarlo Leaf. Mass. (l items), 1908 (Reel 13)
  - Toivo Inki
    - from: John Sainio. Oregon., 1961-1964; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Kalle Salo
    - from: Kalle Salo. photo, 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Saara Tuomi
    - from: Karl Tuomi. N.Y., 1918; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Irja Hellstedt
    - from: Maria Ruohonen. Mass., 1956-1958; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Liisa Kulmanen
    - from: Teodor Markula. Fin, 1929; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Kalle Nieminen
    - from: Hilda Pudas. Ironwood, Mich., 1946; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Elina Santanen
    - from: Hilda Pudas. Ironwood, Mich., 1949; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Terttu Juuri
    - from: Martha Renvall. Ill., 1962; 1 items (Reel 13)
  - Olga Kojonen
    - from: Anna Ylismaki. Col., 1911; 5 items (Reel 13)
  - Aino Mäkilä
    - from: Hulda Davis, Anna KurVinen. N.Y., Del., 1933; 9 items (Reel 13)
  - Evert Haavisto
    - from: Urho Haavisto. Minn., 1938-1948; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Wenneri Haavisto
    - from: Evert Haavisto. Mass., 1962; 7 items (Reel 13)
  - Niilo Uusitalo
    - from Eli Korpi. Minn., 1964; 3 items (Reel 13)
  - Kalle Ylimaa
    - from: Manda Junnila. Mass., Wash., 1950-1962; 7 items (Reel 13)
  - Eeva-Maija Mäkinen
    - from: Elsie Heiken. N.Y., Ohio, 1914-1932; 14 items (Reel 13)
    - from Lydia Lehtinen
      - Ohio, Minn., 1914-1915; 3 items (Reel 13)
      - Detroit, Mich., 1915; 1 items (Reel 13)
      - Ohio, Pa., 1916-1954; 9 items (Reel 13)
  - Urho Nurmi
    - from: Elsie Landa. Minn., 1947; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Jussi Penttilä
    - from: Evert Haavisto. Mass., 1961-1962; 2 items (Reel 13)
  - Hilja Nieminen
    - from: Helmi Huuki. Ont., 1947-1948; 4 items (Reel 13)
  - Maria Hämäläinen
    - from: Maria Tammilehto. Fla., 1948-1961; 3 items (Reel 13)
  - Jenny Jokinen
    - from: Martta Hjalmarsen. N.Y., 1959-1969; 3 items (Reel 13)
  - Maria Savo
    - from: Victor Bock. Ohio, 1922-1924; 10 items (Reel 13)
    - from: Victor Bock. Ohio, Md., 1924-1962; 24 items (Reel 14)
  - Anna Simola
    - from: Lempi Simola. Ont., 1947-1969; 5 items (Reel 14)
    - from: Eemeli Simola. Ont., 1934; 1 items (Reel 14)
  - Helena Raitanen
    - from: Artturi Saari. Ont., Que., B.C., 1926-1937; 11 items (Reel 14)
  - Helmi Häkli
    - from: Hilja Lankinen., undated; 4 items (Reel 14)
  - Väinö Mattila
    - from: Helmi Lindgren. Ont., N.Y., 1957-1963; 7 items (Reel 14)
  - Olga Julkunen
    - from: Elsie Hermanson. Que., 1964; 2 items (Reel 14)
  - Selma Leppäaho
    - from: Martti Setälä. Negaunee, Mich., 1953; 2 items (Reel 14)
    - from: Lahja Setala. Republic, Mich., 1954-1956; 2 items (Reel 14)
  - Veera Länsipää
    - from: Meeri Lehtinen. Mass., Ont., Ore., B.C.:, 1955-1963; 24 items (Reel 14)
  - Eero Kurki
    - from: Rauha Nieminen. Ont., 1959-1963; 2 items (Reel 14)
  - Anna Lukka
    - from: Pekka Utunen. Alta., 1956-1963; 11 items (Reel 14)
  - Rauha Korvenpää, Yrjö Niemell
    - from: Inkeri Mäkelä, Kerkko Tuomi. Pa., 1956-1964; 2 items (Reel 14)
  - Saara Tuomi
    - from: Kerkko Tuomi. Pa., 1957; 1 items (Reel 14)
- Mellilä, letters to
  - Eero Haapala
    - from: William Jalonen. Minn., 1958-1964; 12 items (Reel 14)
  - Väinö Järvinen
    - from: Kalle Ylisto, Matti Jarvinen. Mont., 1938-1939; 5 items (Reel 14)
  - Alli Uotila
    - from: Martta Levo. Ont., 1948-1964; 48 items (Reel 14)
    - from: Hilda Lahde. Ont., 1924-1952; 49 items (Reel 14)
    - from: Hilda Lahde. Ont., 1952-1962; 49 items (Reel 14)
  - Helena Mäki
    - from: unnamed. Mass., Del., 1929-1935; 17 items (Reel 14)
    - from: unnamed. Del., 1935-1963; 42 items (Reel 15)
  - Tauno Gustafson
    - from: Mary Petterson. N.Y., N.J., 1935-36, 4 items (Reel 15)
  - Sylvi Ikävalko
    - from: Linda Singer, 1962; 1 items (Reel 15)
- Merikarvia, letters to
  - Josefiina Heinonen
    - from: Oskar Heinonen. Ont., B.C., 1887-1897; 24 items (Reel 15)
    - from: various. East Lake, Mich., 1890; 3 items (Reel 15)
    - from: A. Eriksson. East Lake, Mich., 1890; 1 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Johan Parkkomaki. B.C., 1895-99, 7 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Jani Koski. B.C.: 1897-1898, 2 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Herman Viikila. B.C., 1896; 3 items (Reel 15)
  - Oskar Heinonen
    - from: Josefiina Heinonen. Fin, 1887; 8 items (Reel 15)
    - from: various. Finland, Wash., 1887-1891; 20 items (Reel 15)
    - from: various. Ont., B.C:, 1887-1893; 7 items (Reel 15)
    - from: The Scandinavian & Finland Emigration Co., Ltd. N.Y., 1892; 1 items (Reel 15)
    - from: Oldenburg-Jasberg Co., 1893 (Reel 15)
  - Toivo Lehtinen
    - from: Venla Karvonen. Ohio, Ont., 1949-1952; 10 items (Reel 15)